thecentsableshoppin.com 2017-06-29

# Disclosure & Privacy Policy

## **Disclosure**

Welcome to my  blog (or, shall we say website) called “Cents’Able Shoppin”.  My priority is to provide you with money-saving deals on things that will help you keep more cash in your pocket.  In doing so, I spend a great majority of my day – not only researching deals, but also validating deals – sometimes in excess of 15-16 hours a day.

I do enjoy what I do, but it does entail quite a bit of time away from the 4 beautiful kiddos I have.  In running this site, there are two ways to compensate the owner/writer of the site (who is me!):

1\. To charge you a monthly fee

OR…

2.  To use advertising

The second option, advertising, allows YOU, the reader, to access the information for free.  I know you are trying very hard to save your family money, and because I do not want to charge for this site, I have chosen the second option.

In doing so, I have had to place a small amount of advertising on this site – some of it will be more obvious, and some – not so obvious – as it’ll be embedded in the post text.  This disclosure policy is my effort in letting you know that some of the deals I bring to you will entail me receiving a small amount of compensation.

The revenue from this site covers the costs that I have to upkeep the site:  the coupon database, hosting fees, the storage space for media – so on and so forth.  Most of all, it compensates me for the time I spend away from my family trying to bring you the best deals out there.

With that being said,  I try very hard to bring you legitimate deals that will bring the most savings to your budget. I will never post anything that I personally would not buy myself.

This disclosure policy was last updated on January 1, 2014.

## **  
Privacy Policy for The CentsAble Shoppin’**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at centsableshoppin@gmail.com.

The CentsAble Shoppin’ values the privacy of our visitors and it is very importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by this website and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other web sites, www.thecentsableshoppin.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
The CentsAble Shoppin’ does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our website visitors based on their visit to The CentsAble Shoppin’ and other sites on the Internet.

Visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include; Google Adsense, Commission Junction, Escalate Media Network, Linkshare, My Savings, Logical Media, and Amazon.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology  to send the advertisements and links that appear on The CentsAble Shoppin’ directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

The CentsAble Shoppin’ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This CentsAble Shoppin’ privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at your browsers’ respective website.

This privacy policy was last updated on January 9, 2015.
